George Dillon Papers
George Dillon Papers
- Memorabilia
  - Scrapbooks
    - "Mr. Dillon", 1925-1928; reviews of Boy in the Wind, miscellaneous printed poems (Box 22)
    - Pulitzer Prize, 1932 (Box 22)
    - "Poetry Magazine" (Box 22)
    - Poems, letters, clippings sent to Adah Hill Dillon, 1933-1937 (Box 22)
    - "A Christmas Letter to G.D. from R.B. and I.B. Washington D.C.", December 1950 (Oversize 2)
    - Clippings, circa 1945-1968; including 1946 book reviews by George Dillon (Oversize 5)
    - Clippings, press reviews of Flowers of Evil (Oversize 1)
    - Theater, clippings of actors and actresses (Oversize 4)
    - Theater, "The Play and the Players", clippings of actors and actresses (Oversize 1)
    - Theater programs and clippings, 1917-1923 (Oversize 5)